we're kind of entering a post-literate society and if like all day long your brain is just smashed
again and again by TikTok of with really upsetting carnage in Gaza then like they're you're talking
and like not to I'm sorry if this is a graphic thing to say but like when I'm trying to make
arguments in favor you know for Israel I realize I'm talking through a wall of dead children
like that's what people are seeing so when I'm like yeah 1.5 civilians for they're just seeing
carnage but that's the emotional blackmail I mean fair enough but like again and that's nice but
like again I'm hearing that through a wall of screaming children it's like it's a I think
it's a harder argument than we we're understanding so I actually really strongly think that like
Jewish day schools should absolutely say no child owns a smartphone until senior year they don't own
one at all period we give it to them senior year and we teach them like this whole not during the
day great nice start no smartphone at all until senior year dumb phone sure like but I think that
we've got to like give our kids brains a chance and their mental health a chance before they start
getting really warped that lady sat there and said we need to give our kids a chance to be brainwashed
without the interference of the truth that's what she said and she said it loud and this was one of
obama speech writers so this is who we're up against I know y'all think we're up against
republicans and democrats no we're up against zionists we're up against people who think like
this and people who enable people to think like this and people who make money off of people who
think like this that's who we're actually up against woo disgusture by the way um speaking of
taking phones baby you need to stop letting them have phones in where you be talking because all
i'm seeing is a torah fails support a real one